

HARUN ALTUN

♥ 2500, LIER, BELGIË 📞 +320499400302

• DETAILS •

2500, Lier België +320499400302 altunhr@gmail.com

> Driving licence B

LINKS

www.altunhr.be

www.linkedin.com/in/harunaltun

https://github.com/harunaltunhr

o SKILLS o

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Git

Node.js

jQuery

MongoDB

React

Bootstrap

Docker

LANGUAGES

Turkish

English

Dutch; Flemish

PROFILE

Junior Developer

After working in HR for 7 years (mainly in IT recruitment) I decided change my route to coding. After completing the bootcamp in HackYourFuture, I started my passion for coding as a web developer. While learning new technologies, I also had the opportunity to develop myself with projects. It is always my greatest ideal to make life easier and do useful work for people

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Quality Controller at Labcorp, Mechelen

January 2022 — Present

Monitoring the quality of the system, machines and production

Web Developer at Bruxelles Decor, Antwerpen

January 2021 — September 2021

Designing and implementing 2 different e-commerce sites,

Set up and develop a stock system for the products in the warehouse

Used Technologies

*Wordpress *HTML *CSS *JavaScript

*Bootstrap *Node.js *SQL

Senior Human Resources Specialist at Silverton HR, London

October 2019 — May 2020

Managing the end to end recruitment processes of IT companies in the USA and Europe,

Conducting interviews with candidates,

Send offers to suitable candidates, sign contracts,

Posting vacancies on job boards

Human Resources Generalist at Huawei Technologies, Turkey

November 2015 — April 2019

End-to-end management of recruitment processes of some departments,

Conducting interviews with candidates,

Posting vacancies on job sites,

Managing HR functions of projects as an HRBP

Recruitment Specialist at Turk Telekom, Turkey

January 2012 — November 2015

Conducting interviews with candidates,

Posting vacancies on job sites,

Updating the CV database

EDUCATION

Environmental Engineering, Istanbul Technical University, Turkey

September 2006 — January 2011

Human Resource Management, Isik University, Turkey

June 2016 — June 2018

Front-End Developer BootCamp, Hack Your Future

May 2020 — January 2021

Technologies I have learned at the end of a total of 9 months of bootcamp;

*HTML *CSS *JavaScript *NodeJs *SQL *GIT *Bootstrap

1 REFERENCES

Evan Cole from Hack Your Future Belgium

evan@hackyourfuture.be